<FTL>

<!-- ///// This file contains all events relating to Axis Station. ///// -->



<!-- /// ENTRY /// -->

<!-- // NORMAL // -->

<!-- // INITIAL // -->



<!-- /// ON-BOARD STRUCTURE /// -->



<!-- /// BOUNTIES /// -->

<!-- // STEALTH // -->

<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_START" unused="true">
	<beaconType id="aa_beacon_axis_bounty" global="true">
		<color r="82" g="161" b="155" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<unvisitedTooltip>The location stated in your bounty from Axis Station.</unvisitedTooltip>
	<text planet="PLANET_POPULATED_SMALL">As the torrent of stars fades back to realspace, your sensors don't immediately indicate anything amiss. That changes, however, as multiple hails begin to flood in. Two other ships at the beacon are bickering back and forth, a Shell Radiant shuttle and an MFK Ace vessel, and it's pretty obvious a fight will break out soon - especially when the Radiant turns to you, seeking protection!</text>
	<ship load="AA_SHIP_REBEL_SELITE_STEALTH" hostile="false"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Defend the Radiants!</text>
		<event>
			<text>The silver-clad Ace recoils as you fly into combat range. Its engines roar to life, and a powerful array of weaponry springs from its hull! You can only hope the risk is worth the reward as you stare down the Rebels' finest.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>This seems like a bad idea.</text>
		<event>
			<text>As chaos erupts and the two ships begin to fire at each other, you decide not to get involved despite the draw of the bounty. The fighting gets so heated that the Radiant tries to jump out, with the Ace pursuing like a mad dog. Whatever they were carrying must have been pretty important...</text>
			<instantEscape/>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<ship name="AA_SHIP_REBEL_SELITE_STEALTH" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_REBEL_SELITE_FIGHT">
	<destroyed>
		<text>A final strike to the ship causes it to briefly erupt into a ball of fire, scattering smoldering chunks of hull ready to be harvested as per protocol.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Contact the Radiant.</text>
			<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_INFO">
				<text>The turquoise light from the Radiant's core makes you feel sick just looking at it, though you know that's just how they are. A deep, thick voice sounds out over the intercom. "Well, well, not a moment too soon! Didn't thhhink I'd see someone packing so much heat... but thhhat just makes thhhings easier."</text>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>What are you talking about?</text>
					<event>
						<text>"Oh, well... it's a bit of a... clandestine matter, if you can believe it. Thhhere's a piece of cargo thhhat we need help withhh, and it's holding some really nasty stuff, really, reeeeally nasty..."</text>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>What does it contain?</text>
							<event>
								<text>"I don't know myself, but I was instructed to point you towards someone who does. Our head scientist back at base should know more!" The Radiant perks up, typing in a string of coordinates and sending them over.</text>
								<quest event="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_STATION"/>
							</event>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>As the last soldier slumps over, you find the ship safe to enter. It's well-kept, organized, and somewhat spartan, though the essential components are worth salvaging.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Contact the Radiants.</text>
			<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_INFO"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>



<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_STATION">
	<beaconType id="aa_beacon_axis_bounty" global="true">
		<color r="82" g="161" b="155" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<unvisitedTooltip>The location sent to you by the Shells.</unvisitedTooltip>
	<text planet="PLANET_POPULATED_GRASSY">The coordinates take you within the airspace of a rather sizable compound, broadcasting all sorts of signals on every frequency.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Hail the station.</text>
		<event>
			<text>As soon as you mention a Radiant scout ship, the control tower gives you the all-clear to land, and a small tender rises from the station to guide you to the safest dock. The scenery is rather pretty, greenery and brick intertwining with modern steel construction. A party of several guards, both human and Shell, hurry you into the office of the head scientist.</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS">
	<text>The figure in front of you was short, looking somewhat comical as he swiveled around to face you, offering a handshake and dismissing the guards. "So these are the Renegades Quasar sent my way... It's a pleasure to meet you, my name is Dr. Corin!"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Leaning forward, he begins to speak. "I'm sure he's already told you about what we're looking for help with, yes?"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Definitely.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Excellent. Well, I have a feeling you're on some time pressure, what with the pesky Rebels on their Renegade-hunting initiative... but I'm open to any questions you'd like to ask about this mission!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_QUESTIONS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Nope.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Dang it, I told him to tell you... Anyway, I have a feeling you're on some time pressure, what with the pesky Rebels on their Renegade-hunting initiative... but I'm open to any questions you'd like to ask about this mission!"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_QUESTIONS"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_QUESTIONS">
	<text>Dr. Corin leans back in his chair, eagerly awaiting your questions.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>What are we helping with?</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_VIRUS"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>What is this place?</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_COMPOUND"/>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_virus" lvl="1">
		<text>Where are we taking the asset?</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_LOCATION"/>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_virus" lvl="1">
		<text>Why are you experimenting on this virus?</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_REASON"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We have no further questions.</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_END"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_VIRUS">
	<text>"Glad you asked. It's a box, containing a sample of one of the most dangerous pathogens ever recorded in the galaxy's history: the Pale Virus. You remember the Rusting Hulks incident?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Yup!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Well, that saves us a bit of time. Long story short, that wasn't the only apocalypse R.S.T. nearly had, and that's not counting the times they almost sunk their own island. Pinnacle mining operations unearthed the Pale from the ice prior to the Hulks, and a single spread particle on a boat was all it took to kill thousands!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Oh...</text>
				<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_VIRUS_CONT">
					<text>"Yeah. According to my case file, there were even reports of Phoenix Park experimenting with DNA splicing to grant themselves immunity, and it only made the situation worse, requiring some cleanup after it was done. Pinnacle themselves weren't hit hard, though, and the situation was stabilized with their help. Without them... I don't think I'd be here today!"</text>
					<variable name="aa_axis_bounty_virus" op="set" val="1"/> <!-- / The player now knows about the Pale Virus. / -->
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event>
							<loadEvent>AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_QUESTIONS</loadEvent>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>No.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Ah. It's not really necessary to know, buuut... it involved Renegades in gigantic mecha punching out equally large bugs. Long story short, that wasn't the only apocalypse R.S.T. nearly had, and that's not counting the times they almost sunk their own island. Pinnacle mining operations unearthed the Pale from the ice prior to the Hulks, and a single spread particle on a boat was all it took to kill thousands!"</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Oh...</text>
				<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_VIRUS_CONT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_COMPOUND">
	<text>"Its official name is the Thunderbolt Biotechnology Research Compound, but we just call it the Lab. My dad, bless his soul, set this place up as a joint effort between humans and Shells to advance genetic sciences, with a specialization in researching pathogens and symptoms."</text>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_virus" lvl="0" max_lvl="0">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Our most secret research project is the topic of today... we need an asset to be protected thanks to a recent data leak, and you're the closest ship we know of that has the capability to defend it."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Asset?</text>
				<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_VIRUS"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Where are we taking it?</text>
				<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_LOCATION"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_virus" lvl="1">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"Our most secret research project is the topic of today... a sample of the Pale Virus is set to be transported to a safer place just in case unsavory parties check the place out."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Why are you researching it?</text>
				<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_REASON"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Where are we taking it?</text>
				<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_LOCATION"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_LOCATION">
	<text>"We need help taking that box to an associate allll the way over in Node 17. There's an affiliated lab close to the Federation Capital that we're scheduling a delivery for, but a recent data leak has forced our hand at protecting it on the way. After all, the Rebels would obviously want it gone, and the Coalition... ugh, I don't even want to think about it."</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_QUESTIONS</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_REASON">
	<text>"Because that virus interfaces with the human geonome like no other. It's highly specialized, but it could be modified to create beneficial organisms and ease the interface of other biological components! It'd help medicines, cybernetics, virtual reality... the data alone could revolutionize the galaxy."</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<loadEvent>AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_QUESTIONS</loadEvent>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_END">
	<text>"Excellent." Dr. Corin stretches, putting away his case file and pressing a couple of buttons on his desk.</text>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_virus" lvl="0" max_lvl="0">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I'm honestly surprised you didn't ask about what the asset was. What I can say is... don't open it. It's a biohazard of ridiculous proportion, and we need to take it to a lab in Node 17 to keep it away from some unsavory parties. Guard it with your life - because the life of the Federation might depend on it."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_END_CONT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_virus" lvl="1">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>"I'm glad that I could tell you about the risks. I have a feeling you understand the gravity of the situation, so I won't waste any more time."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_END_CONT"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_DISCUSS_END_CONT">
	<text>"We'll load the box onto your ship. Thanks for coming out here and hearing me out!" Dr. Corin stands up, waving farewell as you turn away, and you return back to the ship. As thanks for your time, some of the facility's crew give your ship a quick refueling.</text>
	<jumpEvent loop="false" priority="0">AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_ALARM</jumpEvent>  
	<autoReward level="MED">fuel_only</autoReward>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_ALARM">
	<text>As you prepare to leave the beacon, the entire facility suddenly erupts into a cacophony of scarlet lights and blaring klaxons. Human and Shell guards swarm across the hangar, drawing their weapons, and you see Dr. Corin rushing to your ship, waving his arms.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>What's going on?</text>
		<event>
			<text>"The asset's gone! The control tower told me a ship passed over, but there's no way they should have known where it was! No evidence of boarders, no ID on the vessel, just an FTL signature to triangulate with. I'm coming with - I will personally see to it that the box is safe."</text>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="human_medic">Dr. Corin</crewMember>
			<quest event="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>



<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE"> <!-- / TO-DO: Implement a blue option sequence to skip boss fight / -->
	<beaconType id="aa_beacon_axis_bounty" global="true">
		<color r="82" g="161" b="155" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<unvisitedTooltip>The location estimated by the research station. Expect heavy resistance.</unvisitedTooltip>
	<text planet="PLANET_RINGS">You jump to the coordinates, into the atmosphere of a desolate planet. Underneath are the ruins of a once-thriving city, with a massive tower belonging to some long-dead company overlooking the scene. Though the view of the sunrise is wonderful, there isn't really much else to note, as a sensor sweep shows.</text>
	<choice>
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<ship load="AA_RENEGADE_STEALTH_QUEST" hostile="false"/>
			<text>In the distance, you see your target uncloak next to the tower: a sleek stealth cruiser with an odd, half-finished paint job. Its visor gleams in the sunlight, and its captain, an aging man with white hair and a gas mask, hails you.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>"A Renegade, huh? They're serious about this... it's just a few particles of a virus! What do you want from us?"</text>
					<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_virus" lvl="1">
						<text>We're here to take back the samples.</text>
						<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_FIGHT"/>
					</choice>
					<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_virus" lvl="0" max_lvl="0">
						<text>Virus?</text>
						<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_EXPLAIN"/>
					</choice>
					<choice blue="false" hidden="true">
						<text>What are you doing with the box?</text>
						<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_NEGOTIATE"/>
					</choice>
					<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="1">
						<text>Like heck I'm staying here for whatever this is.</text>
						<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_REFUSE"/>
					</choice>
					<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="0" max_lvl="0">
						<text>Like heck I'm staying here for whatever this is.</text>
						<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_REFUSE_NOCORIN"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_FIGHT">
	<text>"Then there is no reason to continue talking. Renegades like you give me such a headache..." A full armament of anti-personnel weaponry springs from their hull - you'll have to tread carefully if you want to survive!</text>
	<playMusic>sylvan</playMusic> <!-- / Placeholder. / -->
	<ship hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_EXPLAIN">
	<text>"He really didn't tell you? Wooow... well, the box contains a virus that kills humans. Simple as that, I can see why he sealed it so tightly."</text>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>We cannot trust you with the box.</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_FIGHT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>What are you doing with the samples?</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_NEGOTIATE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="1">
		<text>This sounds horrible, I'm out of here.</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_REFUSE"/>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="0">
		<text>This sounds horrible, I'm out of here.</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_REFUSE_NOCORIN"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_NEGOTIATE">
	<text>"Well, probably the same as the facility that sent you, running some tests to see how we can use its contents. The term 'bioweapon' comes to mind, but almost anything could come out of it."</text>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true">
		<text>I can't let you do that.</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_FIGHT"/>
	</choice>
	<choice blue="false" hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="1">
		<text>Screw this.</text>
		<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_REFUSE"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_REFUSE">
	<text>Dr. Corin clenches his fists, fuming in the background. He rushes out, and security footage shows him attempting to use an escape pod. The stealth cruiser's captain doesn't seem too bothered by the interruption, and decides to end the transmission, jumping away soon after. It feels strange dropping out so close to the end, with such a dangerous situation and no reward to show for it.</text>
	<instantEscape/>
	<removeCrew class="human_medic">
		<clone>false</clone>
		<text>Dr. Corin cannot be cloned, as he is still alive, no matter how poorly he might feel about the situation.</text>
	</removeCrew>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_REFUSE_NOCORIN">
	<text>The stealth cruiser's captain doesn't seem too bothered by the interruption, and decides to end the transmission, jumping away soon after. It feels strange dropping out so close to the end, with such a dangerous situation and no reward to show for it.</text>
	<instantEscape/>
	<choice>
		<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
		<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Do nothing.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<!-- / BOSS SHIP EVENTS / -->

<ship name="AA_RENEGADE_STEALTH_QUEST" auto_blueprint="AA_RENEGADE_STEALTH_QUEST">
	<triggeredEvent event="AA_RENEGADE_STEALTH_ESCAPE" enemyHull="10" enemyCrew="3"/> <!-- / Handles escape event. / -->
	<miniBoss sound="victory" musicDelay="-1"/>
	<escape chance="1" min="10" max="10" load="AA_RENEGADE_STEALTH_ESCAPE"/>
	<gotaway load="AA_RENEGADE_STEALTH_GOTAWAY"/>
	<destroyed>
		<playMusic/>
		<text>The Stealth Cruiser begins to fall out of the sky as a wing breaks off, its glass-like hull armor shattering into small pieces. It spirals out of control, and its FTL drive violently explodes in a glorious display of blue fire. You've won!</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Search the crash site.</text>
			<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DESTROY"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<playMusic/>
		<text>The last fighter onboard slumps over, giving you the time you need to rush the engine room and shut off the ship's jump drive. You've won!</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Inspect the inside of the ship.</text>
			<event load="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DEADCREW"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>
<event name="AA_RENEGADE_STEALTH_ESCAPE">
	<text>"Damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it! We can't fight these guys, we've got to get out of here!" The remaining crew frantically mash at the controls, triggering their FTL drive. They're going to get away!</text>
	<loadEscape force="true"/>
</event>
<event name="AA_RENEGADE_STEALTH_GOTAWAY">
	<text>One moment, the ship is here. Another, and it has slipped from your grasp. You were too late to stop the Renegades, and they've fled with their haul in tow.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="1">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>Dr. Corin falls to his knees, stunned. "No... no, no, no! Well... this place is gonna be a lot worse off without a good eye on that box, and I have a feeling that our facility won't be doing so hot. I guess... I'm staying here for the time being. After, though? Who knows?"</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="0">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>With nothing else to do, you sigh and order another jump. Though the loss is disheartening, you and your crew know that there is still an even more important mission to finish.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DESTROY"> <!-- / Checks if Corin is still alive. / -->
	<loadEventList first="true" default="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DESTROY_NOCORIN">
		<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DESTROY_CORIN" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="1"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DESTROY_CORIN">
	<text>While harvesting the crash site, you find plenty of useful odds and ends to go around, including one of the ship's weapons which survived the crash. After a good search, you and Dr. Corin find the asset you're looking for, sealed in an armored box decorated with tacky, caution-stripe tape and a simple label.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<weapon name="AA_ENERGY_RAD"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you and your crew wrap up the fight, Quasar jumps into the system bearing a much larger ship - a Radiant Cruiser! Setting the vessel down on the surface to inspect the damage, he rolls out to meet you as Dr. Corin packs his box back onto your ship. The Radiant shakes your hand, and pays up for your bounty.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>Dr. Corin waves to Quasar as he leaves, then turns to you. "Well, I'm not too sure how the facility will fare with Rebel patrols catching up, and our reputation tanking from the leaks... but after a performance like that, I'd be happy to stick with you for the rest of your journey."</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DESTROY_NOCORIN">
	<text>While harvesting the crash site, you find plenty of useful odds and ends to go around, including one of the ship's weapons which survived the crash. After a good search, you find the asset you're looking for, sealed in an armored box decorated with tacky, caution-stripe tape and a simple label.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<weapon name="AA_ENERGY_RAD"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you and your crew wrap up the fight, Quasar jumps into the system bearing a much larger ship - a Radiant Cruiser! Setting the vessel down on the surface to inspect the damage, he rolls out to meet you as you pack the box back onto your ship. The Radiant shakes your hand, and pays up for your bounty, though they seem rather somber about the whole ordeal.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>As Quasar rolls to his ship, he stops, turning to you one more time. "I'm... not too sure how thhhe facility will fare withhhh Rebel patrols catching up, especially withhhh ol' Corin gone... and I'm not too sure where else I could find anywhere to work. Mind having a Radiant staying over?"</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="shell_radiant">Quasar</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DEADCREW"> <!-- / Checks if Corin is still alive. / -->
	<loadEventList first="true" default="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DEADCREW_NOCORIN">
		<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DEADCREW_CORIN" req="aa_axis_bounty_corin" lvl="1"/>
	</loadEventList>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DEADCREW_CORIN">
	<text>Passing through the interior, you call off the initial harvesting operation when you and Dr. Corin find the ship's laboratory, miraculously undamaged. The databanks and sample storage tell tales of mysterious experiments onboard that put even the Shells' grand genetic projects to shame! Corin retrieves from the corner his box, labeled with tacky, caution-striped tape and a simple label.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<weapon name="AA_ENERGY_RAD"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you and your crew wrap up the fight, Quasar jumps into the system bearing a much larger ship - a Radiant Cruiser! Setting the vessel down on the surface to inspect the damage, he gazes in awe at the intact laboratory, and decides to stay a while to download the data, paying your bounty handsomely alongside a special gift: a... piece of one of his experiments.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="blob">Kijoop</crewMember>
			<choice>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>Dr. Corin waves to Quasar as he leaves, then turns to you. "Well, I'm not too sure how the facility will fare with Rebel patrols catching up, and our reputation tanking from the leaks... but after a performance like that, I'd be happy to stick with you for the rest of your journey."</text>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="AA_BOUNTY_STEALTH_FINALE_END_DEADCREW_NOCORIN">
	<text>Passing through the interior, you call off the initial harvesting operation when you find the ship's laboratory, miraculously undamaged. The databanks and sample storage tell tales of mysterious experiments onboard that put even the Shells' grand genetic projects to shame! You retrieve Corin's box from a corner of the room, labeled with tacky, caution-striped tape and a simple label.</text>
	<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
	<weapon name="AA_ENERGY_RAD"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event>
			<text>As you and your crew wrap up the fight, Quasar jumps into the system bearing a much larger ship - a Radiant Cruiser! Setting the vessel down on the surface to inspect the damage, he gazes in awe at the intact laboratory, and calls out a small gray blob to follow him. Though he seems rather somber, he still takes the time to download and harvest everything he can from the laboratory.</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
			<crewMember amount="1" class="blob">Kijoop</crewMember>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event>
					<text>As Quasar rolls to his ship, he stops, turning to you one more time. "I'm... not too sure how thhhe facility will fare withhhh Rebel patrols catching up, especially withhhh ol' Corin gone... and I'm not too sure where else I could find anywhere to work.  Mind having a Radiant and a Morph staying over?"</text>
					<crewMember amount="1" class="shell_radiant">Quasar</crewMember>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

</FTL>