<FTL>

<!-- ///// This file contains all events relating to the Provision sector. All events relating to Axis are instead found in their own file. ///// -->



<!-- /// SECTOR ENTRY /// -->

<event name="AA_START_PROVISION"> <!-- /// DUMMY, IDENTICAL TO AUGMENTED GUARD /// -->
	<metaVariable name="juke_augmented" op="set" val="1"/>
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_start" global="false">
		<color r="46" g="252" b="51" a="1"/>
	</beaconType>
	<text>You awake to find yourself facing a large Lanius guard, colored same as the ship before. Your new Lanius friend fiddles with your translator so you can understand them properly.</text>
	<variable name="loc_unique_sectors" op="add" val="1"/>
	<achievement silent="false">ACH_TRUEEND_AUGMENTED</achievement>
	<ship load="SHIP_GUARD_AUGMENTED" hostile="false"/>
	<changeBackground>BACK_SECTOR_AUGMENTED</changeBackground>
	<playSound>lightspeed</playSound>
	<remove name="HIDDEN DUMMY"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="GUARD_AUGMENTED"/>
	</choice>
</event>



<!-- /// SECTOR EXIT /// -->



<!-- /// FRIENDLY EVENTS (never have a fight) /// -->



<!-- /// NEUTRAL EVENTS (might have a fight) /// -->



<!-- /// HOSTILE EVENTS (always have a fight) /// -->

<!-- // REBEL SHIP FIGHT // -->

<event name="AA_ENCOUNTER_PROVISION_REBEL">
	<text load="AA_TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PROVISION_REBEL"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_REBEL_FIGHT" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="AA_TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PROVISION_REBEL">
	<text>Even in such a heavily secured sector, the Rebels have proven to be stubborn as always. A Rebel ship that slipped through the cracks of the sector's entry point spots you, and turns to attack!</text>
	<text>You couldn't mistake it if you tried. The blazing orange hull of a Rebel vessel flits about an Auto-ship of Dustworm make, analyzing its composition, but immediately reverses direction when you show up to the beacon.</text>
	<text>Hiding behind a nearby asteroid is a Rebel ship. Weapons spring from its hull, and it broadcasts a loud slur over your intercom in an attempt to disorient you.</text>
	<text>You receive a hail from a vessel. The captain reveals it to be of Rebel design, and spews a cold, yet childish one-liner as you turn around to face it. "Nothing personal, kiddo!"</text>
	<text>No matter where you flee to, there's one constant you can always rely on: there will be a Rebel ship at most three beacons away from you. You wonder if their travel technologies could be used for better purposes than crusading against all non-humans.</text>
	<text>You arrive at the beacon just a second too late. A Rebel ship flies directly at you out of a massive, blue fireball, presumably from some Dustworm civilian vessel it just blew up. Battle stations!</text>
</textList>

<!-- // PIRATE SHIP FIGHT // -->

<event name="AA_ENCOUNTER_PROVISION_PIRATE">
	<text load="AA_TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PROVISION_PIRATE"/>
	<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<textList name="AA_TEXT_ENCOUNTER_PROVISION_PIRATE">
	<text>If there's one thing you can expect from pirates, it's that they will always be everywhere you go. A small pirate ship barrels right at you from a nearby moon.</text>
	<text>As you jump into the beacon, you nearly ram into a pirate ship that slipped by the ever-watchful Provisional Government. Though you're both confused as to what just happened, the smaller vessel decides that they won't pass up such an opportunity...</text>
	<text>You encounter a pirate ship harassing a Dustworm mining ship. Their engines sputter for a moment as they turn to face your ship, seeing nothing but a bigger payout.</text>
	<text>A Dustworm vessel rockets past your viewscreen, immediately followed by a pirate vessel. Seeing your ship, they turn to face you, weapons primed and ready to protect themselves from you.</text>
	<text>There is only a single ship at this otherwise empty beacon. Owned by a band of pirates, it opens fire as soon as it sees a potential victim.</text>
	<text>Jumping into the beacon, you spot a pirate ship ducking out of range of a nearby A.T.L.A.S. vessel. When the patrol jumps away to inspect another beacon, it immediately springs to life!</text>
</textList>



<!-- /// MORALITY UPDATES /// -->

<event name="AA_MORALITY_UPDATE_PROVISION">
	<text>[NOTORIETY INCREASED - PROVISIONAL GOVERNMENT]
	Your actions here, justifiable or not, will not reflect well in the eyes of the Provisional Government or its citizens. Continuously perform actions like this and you might start to see negative reactions from the Provisional Government and its allies.</text>
	<variable name="aa_rep_provision" op="add" val="1"/>
</event>
<event name="AA_MORALITY_UPDATE_PROVISION_FIGHT">
	<text>[NOTORIETY INCREASED - PROVISIONAL GOVERNMENT]
	Your actions here, justifiable or not, will not reflect well in the eyes of the Provisional Government or its citizens. Continuously perform actions like this and you might start to see negative reactions from the Provisional Government and its allies.</text>
	<variable name="aa_rep_provision" op="add" val="1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="AA_MORALITY_REMOVE_PROVISION">
	<text>[NOTORIETY DECREASED - PROVISIONAL GOVERNMENT]
	You have done a good deed here in the eyes of the Provisional Government. If you've gained notoriety from other actions in the past, you're more likely to be forgiven for them.</text>
	<variable name="aa_rep_provision" op="add" val="-1"/>
</event>
<event name="AA_MORALITY_REMOVE_PROVISION_FIGHT">
	<text>[NOTORIETY DECREASED - PROVISIONAL GOVERNMENT]
        You have done a good deed here in the eyes of the Provisional Government. If you've gained notoriety from other actions in the past, you're more likely to be forgiven for them.</text>
	<variable name="aa_rep_provision" op="add" val="-1"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>
</event>



</FTL>